the head of drinking is the playing ground and restaurant culture
喝酒的头是运动场和餐厅文化
beam drink in the morning inez and always stay in which arthur rose already ow en
上午inez喝束酒，并一直呆在亚瑟玫瑰已经喝完了
xchange for carriage and an extra ordinary yes call it i to be
xchange的运输和一个额外的普通是称它为
merry and happy yes any watches that innovations the
快乐和快乐是任何创新的手表
sole drivers and mixer forget about a probes
独家司机和调音师忘了探针
at least for a while but it also dampens the census
至少有一段时间，但它也使人口普查受挫
reviews charming capabilities impair sar motor skills and the basically
评论迷人的能力会损害sar的运动技能，并且基本上
help system i feel even looked about drink and s or late to file it
帮助系统，我什至看过酒后就迟到了
and the trap of alcohol sms min destroying millions of life's so fine hugh
和酒精短信的陷阱分钟摧毁了数百万人的生命
zabriskie joy of drinking that he is debilitating effects or everywhere
喝酒的zabriskie欢乐，他使人衰弱或无处不在
doing so for hawkers of trillium meursing or even in the precious times
甚至在珍贵的时期也可以这样做
with the universal given to was live so could die scaping the experience of
有了万能的生命，所以可能会死掉
life in all thrones or everything emotionally highs and lows
生活在所有宝座或情感高潮中的一切
is joyce and hardships andrew just enjoy life is the camp
是欢乐与艰辛，是安德鲁，只是享受生活，是大本营
chocolate as much as you enjoy this date of drunkenness
您喜欢这个醉酒之日的巧克力
or simply put how can we get drunk on life
或简单地讲我们如何才能醉酒
years ago hard douwes theo builds leading sheds
多年前艰难的杜威斯（the douwes theo）建造了领先的棚屋
up with computers and buddha in the tea house
在茶馆里坐电脑和佛
and you're sitting together at table de weer of er thomas special drink
和你一起坐在托马斯·德·托马斯特别饮料的餐桌旁
gold deuce of life i immediately buddha reject this sound and scholarship death
生命的金子般的瞬间我立刻拒绝了这种声音和奖学金的死亡
and life or as offering another drinking pot is the deuce of life
与生命或提供另一个饮水器是生命的缩影
definitely not worth taking smr effect is a light a coin with freedom of the
绝对不值得采取smr效果是一枚具有自由之光的硬币
wheel of suffering so corn oil knife orchestra oakley and ministry the pain that he lives
苦难的车轮使玉米油刀乐队奥克利服侍他所生活的痛苦
it was crawl come us then set daddy pig and george de
它是爬行来我们然后设置爸爸猪和乔治·德
drink before i tested it you say the didn't like the
在我测试之前先喝点饮料，然后说不喜欢
test en al-boerdaa your right something is wrong is bitter is miserable
测试en-boerdaa你的正确，有些事情是错的，是苦的，是痛苦的
it's not worth drinking ben piloting hit the ball and hit it
本不值得喝Ben飞行员将球击中并击中
one goal after that i come up and started to
之后的一个目标是我开始并开始
dance and dance and that's screaming like met me after a while
跳舞，跳舞，过了一会儿就像我见面一样尖叫
i city and return receipt
我所在的城市并返回收据
buddha and confucius have those computers and so test how was it
佛陀和孔子有那些电脑，所以测试一下
sheds and third time i'll go to say a become closet there is nothing to be said
棚子，第三次我要说一个壁橱，没什么可说的
i explained that the buddha was too quick to charge and confused bases
我解释说佛陀充电太快了，基地也混乱了
judgment on a small ships and fury they might be
对一艘小船的判断和他们可能的愤怒
right that is a farmer's software and live
对，这是农民的软件和实时的
beast under doctrine it might be better to avoid shirt en
根据学说的野兽，最好避免穿衬衫
elements of life in order to avoid suffering
为了避免痛苦的生活要素
with in the story d we views drugs ferians live and the million word charlotte off to
在故事d中，我们看到了活着的毒品囚徒和百万字的夏洛特
describe what it really is to be live mens
描述活着的男人到底是什么
there is nothing to be sad and to recharge about life one has to fully
没有什么可悲伤和充实的生活，而必须充实
experience at well that you so credit buddha or computers and der traditions
经验丰富，使您相信佛陀或计算机以及传统知识
watch needless to say content pro found with
观看无需多说的专业人士发现的内容
then the story offers two important messages
然后故事提供了两个重要信息
the first one is not to take religions or radiologically too seriously so that he
第一个是不要对宗教或放射学过于重视，以至于他
platform experiencing life in the rules we ridgid and a break marcel sap
平台按照ridgid和打破marcel sap规则体验生活
flexible it's difficult to move along with
灵活，很难随身携带
existence you have to solo is in phlox s sheds red in the hall beginning and a
你必须独奏的存在是福禄考在大厅开始时掉下了红色，
quote those were stef and ridgid hard
引用那些是Stef和ridgid很难的话
disciples of that those were soft and using earth disciples of life and close
那些柔软的门徒，并使用生活和亲密的大地门徒
the second living is that your experience life with you drink it at once and just
第二种生活是您与您一起体验生活，一次又一次地喝它
that were like like like to dance after drinking and love alcoholic beverages
就像喝完酒后跳舞，喜欢酒精饮料
what old mourns frank and sb substances is an experience that many people
老哀悼的坦率和sb物质是很多人的经历
richard essence become fever which is paradoxically the critters for this your
理查德的本质变得发烧，这自相矛盾的是，这个小动物
life and closing or even or from live perhaps as much for even more so ridgid
生活和结束，甚至甚至是活着，甚至更多
individual dark lannister spiritual person was to
个别的黑暗lannister精神的人是
experience when santas arm took the and join life
圣诞老人手臂接过并加入生活的经历
more by experiencing the lesson is nothing more than an escape
上一堂课，无非是逃脱
it meets them the live earth or emotions in journal during the weekend
在周末，他们在日记中遇到了他们的生活世界或情感
we were said to drink while you're happy to drink
据说我们在您乐意喝酒时喝酒
so this can or drunken nose is a rejection of life by and embrace or a
所以这个可以喝醉的鼻子是对生命的拒绝，拥抱或拥抱
mindset ring substance well getting drunk online is a shoot in
心态戒律很好上网喝醉了
the opposite direction rather than blocking what about wells how
相反的方向而不是阻碍井如何
and widest full spectrum see what people drink after a disease
最广泛的范围可以看到人们患病后喝什么
and bark i could profile bill rollercoaster ride with out where they
和树皮，我可以简述比尔过山车的旅程，而他们不在哪里
wanted venture they want joyful interactions that want
想要冒险，他们想要快乐的互动
to encounter someone attraktiv and by reducing field day off to experience
遇到某人的吸引力，并减少野外休假的时间
that it's easier to meet these things
遇到这些事情比较容易
even though fair a comfortable in a thousand mina death bed is the least
即使至少有一千个Mina死亡床很舒服
buddy's fight or flight 'response is triggered
好友的战斗或逃跑响应被触发
for example, a side effect of entering a new territory which passes when
例如，进入新区域的副作用会在
experience and signs of safety slightly on price pp for chain car for
链条车的价格pp上的经验和安全迹象略有增加
comfort zone what is priceless by your word
舒适地带，用您的话说，无价之宝
loose fit involvement with elements of life
松散地融入生活元素
the election of overcoming foundries did not inverse
克服铸造厂的选举并没有逆转
dennis bottle for keycard because she that anxiety is the dizziness of
丹尼斯瓶的钥匙卡，因为她认为焦虑是头晕
freedom be in drink onlive min z wie your able to fully and cronshaw sleep and
自由饮酒，活着至少可以使您充分睡眠并保持睡眠状态，
joy of life in all kinds of marinus recovery if there is a malfunction in the music
音乐出现故障时，各种海底捞的生活都会充满欢乐
substances or activities to number is already a test that he has experience of
物质或活动的数量已经是他所经历的测试
life is very kind and sometimes it seems to intends to handle and that's where i
生活非常友善，有时似乎打算处理，这就是我
find the key to getting drunk onlive couple riding the wave
找到让醉酒成对的情侣乘风破浪的关键
no matter how big wall rejoicing wanna see school at nat clinging to its high
不管有多高兴，我都想看到学校在紧贴其高处
concern running which is naturally flat now the cipher is deeply put
担心运行，现在密码已经深深地平了
and great war adam the tears of joy when you don't switch or when we get together
和伟大的战争亚当在一起，当您不转身或我们聚在一起时，喜悦的眼泪
see for a long time what is also the skippers one who do
看到很长一段时间，做船长的人也是
something refer the the light of spanning time and nature
某些事物代表了跨越时间和自然的光芒
the content point or not new thing anything more and the flourishing at the
内容点或没有新事物，并在蓬勃发展
pursuit of virtue my christelijk it's not ridgid lee
追求美德不是克里斯·李
standing on the sidelines of experience but est abrogé
站在经验的边缘，但estabrogé
even in the present we would be the nile or as already there dashwood
即使在现在，我们也会成为尼罗河或达什伍德（Dashwood）
replace a resistance to the is a real dollars of life by you welcome in
取代对生命的抵抗，是您生命中的真实财富
curiosity to them this is how we keep get drunk on life bug
对他们的好奇心是我们不断醉酒的方式
ringlet and the paradox is that we can only enjoy life
let和悖论是，我们只能享受生活
feel when you took shows so and 6s we do
感觉当您参加演出时，我们和6s在一起
one week and truck life itself is already the frank in af
一个星期，卡车的寿命已经很久了
john towards wf is open up to date with old resistance and without
约翰方向wf是开放的，有旧的抵抗，没有
touching herself to much to judgments of right and wrong and trends and the
在判断自己是非与否以及趋势和
ideals of photo shoot and shoot life is simply what it is and the
照片拍摄和生活的理想就是它的本质，而
show that we have everything in order you n or today i thousand is fierce
表明我们拥有一切，以便您或今天i凶猛
be enjoyed mode it always said to be suffered the simple he stable life
被称为享受模式，总是说他会过着简单，稳定的生活
thanks for watching
谢谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]
after one time [Music]
一段时间后[音乐]